lockheedfcu.org 2011-06-01

# LOCKHEED FEDERAL CREDIT UNION PRIVACY NOTICE

                           LOCKHEED FEDERAL CREDIT UNION
                                          PRIVACY NOTICE
As a valued member of Lockheed Federal Credit Union, respecting your privacy and the security
of your personal information is very important to us. Please read this Privacy Notice carefully. It is
intended to advise you regarding the types of information we collect, and how the information is
used. By providing this information to you, we want to assure you that we maintain strict security
procedures to protect your information.
Information We Collect About You
To help us serve your financial needs, provide member services, and offer new products and
services, we collect non-public personal information about you from the following sources:
• Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;
• Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others; and
• Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies.
Use of Information
In order to administer, manage and service your account(s) and provide you with products and
services, it is necessary for us to disclose or provide access to Customer Information. We may
disclose all of the information that we collect as described above.
We may also share Customer Information about you with non-affiliated third parties as permitted
by law, and who may help us process transactions or provide customer service for your accounts,
such as preparing or mailing statements or processing transactions. Types of non-affiliates with
which we share information include:
• ATM networks
• Mortgage insurers, escrow and title companies
• In response to a subpoena, a fraud investigation, or other legal process
• Bill payment processors
• Credit reporting agencies
• Check printers
• Data processing companies
• CU Service Centers, another financial institution or entity that purchases your loan or account,
   or if we sell or merge parts of our business
• Technical service consultants
• Regulatory agencies and auditors
We also share Customer Information with companies that perform marketing services on our
behalf or to financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We require
these non-affiliates to agree to maintain appropriate safeguards to protect the confidentiality and
security of your information through the use of confidentiality clauses in our agreements with
them. If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive member, we will adhere to
the privacy policies and practices as described in this notice.
Protecting Your Information

We protect information we collect about you by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural
safeguards. These safeguards restrict access to your confidential customer information to only
those employees who have a specific need to utilize your data. We train our employees on how to
handle your information to maintain the confidentiality and customer privacy.
If You Terminate Your Relationship With Us
If your credit union Membership is terminated we will not share information we have collected
about you, except as permitted or required by law.
Confidentiality and Security
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who have a
specific business in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of
maintaining confidentiality and customer privacy. We maintain physical, electronic and
procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulation and leading industry practices to
safeguard your nonpublic personal information.
Contact Us
Please call us with any questions regarding this Privacy Notice at (800) 328-LFCU. Or you can
write to us at:
                           Lockheed Federal Credit Union
                           Attn: Financial Privacy
                           P.O. Box 10848
                           Burbank, CA 91505
Advertising
If you prefer that the credit union not advertise additional products and services, you may request
to be placed on the do not advertise list by informing a member service representative at (800)
328-LFCU. The credit union will attempt to limit the communication with you to what is legally
required.
Internet Security
The Information We Collect From You When You Browse LFCU web site anonymously: There
are two ways that we gather information about you. First, we do track which pages of our site you
visit and note your IP address (as all web sites do automatically), but do not gather any
information about you as an individual. The general information we gather enables us to serve
you better by continually improving our site based on current use patterns. Second, we also
gather specific information from you when you're interested in our products and services. We
Respect Your Personal Privacy.
We Respect Your Personal Privacy
LFCU knows how important it is that sensitive information about you remains confidential. LFCU
will not exchange general tracking and IP address information collected by our web site with any
companies outside LFCU family of companies without your permission. As a LFCU
Accountholder, you'll receive from time-to-time, valuable product and service offers from us, from
our affiliates, and other well-established companies. We carefully develop these offers to meet
our standards and to assure that they reach Accountholders most likely to take advantage of the
opportunity. To do so, we gather information you provide on your application and from servicing
your home loans or other products and services that may indicate financing and investing

preferences to create marketing lists. We create these lists under conditions designed to protect
the privacy of your information.
Browser Security
Recent versions of most internet browsers support the encrypted transmission of on-line
documents and the data you enter on a web page. This means that instead of sending readable
text, both your browser and the web site's secure server encode all text using a security key. That
way, personal data sent to your browser or data you send back would be extremely difficult to
decode in the unlikely event it was intercepted by an unauthorized party. The key used for
encoding is a random number that is unique to your session at the secure web site. There are two
grades of internet security: International grade encryption uses a 40-bit random number
negotiated between your browser and the web-server. This means that only one out of about
1,000,000,000,000 possible decoding keys can be used to decipher your data. Domestic-grade
encryption uses a 128-bit key, so that the number of possible keys is vastly larger. LFCU site
uses the highest grade of encryption supported by your browser and your Internet connection.
How Do I Know If Security Is Operating?
Your Internet session is encrypted if your security-enabled browser connected to a web site using
the Secure Hypertext Transport Protocol. URL strings beginning with "HTTPS://" instead of the
usual "HTTP://" indicate that the secure protocol is in effect. Your browser may also tell you if
security is operating. For example, Netscape Navigator may display the icon in the lower left
corner of your screen in secure mode. If 128-bit security is in effect, it shows the icon. Microsoft
Internet Explorer shows an icon in either case. Note that security may be operating without any
visible indication if the web page you are viewing employs frames (see below). If secure
transmission is not in effect or only part of a frame-based page is secure, Netscape shows the
"broken key" icon, and Explorer does not show the "lock" icon. Most browsers can be set to give
you a pop-up announcement when you enter or leave a secure web page. In Netscape, these
settings are on the Security Preferences "General" tab. In IE, the setting is on the "Advanced" tab
when you select "Options" on the View menu.
Secure mode and frame based web pages.
Security may be operating without displaying any security icons (or Netscape may show the
"broken key" icon) if only part of a frame-based page is employing security. You can verify the
security of page within a frame by opening it in a new browser window. Both IE and Netscape
allow you to open a link in a new window by right clicking on the link and selecting that option
from the pop-up context menu. When a secure page is open in its own window, instead of being
viewed within a frame, you can then see the security icons provided by your browser as well as
the "https://" secure protocol prefix in the URL string.
                                     CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
The primary goal of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) Rule is to give parents
control over what information is collected from their children online and how such information may
be used. LFCU does not provide online services or web pages directed to children.
Contact Us
Please call us with any questions regarding this Privacy Notice at 800-328-LFCU. Or you can
write to us at:
                                   Lockheed Federal Credit Union

Attn: Financial Privacy
P.O. Box 10848
Burbank, CA 91505
                        CU 13626A--4 3/2007
